Community Cookbook Collection: Local Organization Non-Profit Cookbooks and Nationally-Published Popular Cookbooks, 1907-2008 TX614.C66
Lilly Library
- INDIANA
  - 1. Lin Davis (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Indiana to California: A Recipe Collection from Lin Davis. Description: Recipes from Indiana to California, 1987. Olathe: Cookbook Publishers, INC. 225 p.: ill.by Eve Evans, blank notes section, index; 23 cm. Yellow comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 4)
  - 2. Marion Twp. Rural Fire Dept. Auxiliary (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: If You Can't Stand the Heat...Marion Twp. Rural Fire Department Auxiliary. Title: If You Can't Stand the Heat...A Collection of Recipes by Marion Twp. Rural Fire Dept. Auxiliary. Description: Mitchell, In, 2000. 118 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Red comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 3. M.B.A. Wives Club (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Seasoned Favorites. Title:Seasoned Favorites Compiled by M.B.A. Wives Club, Indiana, University, Bloomington, Indiana. Description: Bloomington, IN, 1969. 123 p.: blank notes section; 22 cm. Bound with two metal rings at top of book, with hand-illustrated cover. (Box Box 4)
  - 4. Monroe County Fair Association, copy 1 (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book: Favorite Recipes from Our Best Cooks. Title: A book of favorite recipes compiled by Monroe County Fair Association in Cooperation with Monroe County Extension Homemakers Association. Description: Kansas City: Circulation Service. 98 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 5. Monroe County Fair Association, copy 2 (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book: Favorite Recipes from Our Best Cooks. Title: A book of favorite recipes compiled by Monroe County Fair Association in Cooperation with Monroe County Extension Homemakers Association. Description: Kansas City: Circulation Service, copyright 1968. 98 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 6. Monroe County History Center (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Mouthwatering Monroe County: More Recipes Collected by the Monroe County History Center. Title: Mouthwatering Monroe County: More Recipes Collected by the Monroe County History Center. Description: Bloomington, IN, 2009. 162 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Green comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 7. Monroe County Public Library (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: A Collection of Personal Recipes Presented by...the staff and friends of the Monroe County Public Library. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 1986. Published by the Monroe County Public Library Foundation. 53 p.; 22 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 4)
  - 8. Mother's Evening (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes of INDIANA. Title: Favorite Recipes of INDIANA. Description: "Contains 800 recipes from Indiana Women's Club Leaders"-Front cover. Montgomery: Favorite Recipes Press, Inc., ~1964. 183 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers and detached section tabs. (Box Box 4)
  - 9. North Group, Symphony Women's Committee, Indiana State Symphony Society, Inc. (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Concertos for Cooks: A Symphony of Favorites. Spine Title: Concertos for Cooks. Title: Concertos for Cooks: A Symphony of Favorite. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1987. Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra. 167 p.: ill., index, notes; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 10. Pike County Bicentennial Committee (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes. Description: Petersburg, Indiana, 1976. Compiled by the Pike County Bicentennial Committee. 208 p.: ill.,; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 4)
  - 11. President Harrison Home (From Caroline's Kitchen) (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: From Caroline's Kitchen. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1976, with a second printing in 1977, which includes First Ladies' Recipes. ~44 p.: ill.; 23 cm. In illustrated wrappers with yarn. (Box Box 4)
  - 12. President Harrison Home (The President Harrison Home Recipes) (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: The President Harrison Home Recipes: From the Past, the Near Past, and the Present. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1984. "Published and Printed by Cookbook Publishers, Inc...Olathe, Kansas"-Verso table of contents. 68 p.: ill., blank pages for notes, index; 23 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 13. Saint Theresa Circle of Saint Peter's Church (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book: Favorite Recipes from Our Best Cooks. Title: A book of favorite recipes compiled by Saint Theresa Circle of Saint Peter's Church. Description: La Porte, Indiana, 1966. Kansas City: Circulation Service. 74 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 14. The Saturday Evening Post (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: The Saturday Evening Post Family Cookbook. Spine Title: The Saturday Evening Post Family Cookbook. Title: The Saturday Evening Post Family Cookbook. Description: Indianapolis, Indiana, 1975. Edited by Julie Nixon Eisenhower and Frederic A. Birmingham. Indianapolis, IN: Curtis Publishing Company, 1975. 154 p.: ill., index; 29 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 4)
  - 15. Spring Mill Bible Camp (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Sharing our Best: Friends of Spring Mill Bible Camp. Title: Sharing our Best: A Collection of Recipes by Friends of Spring Mill Bible Camp. Description: Mitchell, Indiana, 2001. 182 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Blue comb binding, with illustrated boards and section tabs. (Box Box 4)
  - 16. St. Mark's Evangelical and Reformed Church (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: St. Mark's Cook Book. Description: New Albany (?), Indiana. By Delphian Class. 118 p.; 26 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 4)
  - 17. St. Mark's United Methodist Church, copy 1 (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: St. Mark's Treasures: 40th Anniversary, 1994. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 1994. 148 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 4)
  - 18. St. Mark's United Methodist Church, copy 2 (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: St. Mark's Treasures: 40th Anniversary, 1994. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 1994. 148 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 4)
  - 19. Sweet Adelines, Inc., Hoosier Hills Chapter (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes: Sweet Adelines, Inc. (Hoosier Hills Chapter, Bloomington, Indiana, 1979). Description: Bloomington, Indiana 1979. Iowa Falls: General Publishing and Binding. 124 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 4)
  - 20. Tell City Schmeizer Fest (Box Box 4)
    - Cover Title: Tell City Schmeizer Fest Cook Book. Spine Title: Schmeizer Fest Cook Book. Description: Tell City, IN, 1978. Produced by Tell City Schweizer Fest, Inc. Revised ed. Bound in white binder with metal rings. (Box Box 4)
  - 1. Temple Adath Israel Sisterhood (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Years of Tradition: A Treasury of Recipes Compiled by Temple Adath Israel Sisterhood, Evansville, Indiana. Title: Years of Tradition. Description: Evansville, Indiana, 1973-1974. 196 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 2. Thelma Weaver (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Thelma Weaver's Cook Book of the Air. Title: Cook Book of the Air: More than 500 recipes from your friends and neighbors. Description: La Porte, Indiana. 233 p.: illustration (photo of author), index; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 5)
  - 3. Tri Kappa, Alpha Chapter (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Taste of Tri Kappa, Alpha Chapter. Spine Title: Taste of Tri Kappa. Title: Taste of Tri Kappa: A Collection of Recipes by Tri Kappa, Alpha Chapter. Description: Bloomington, Indiana, 2004. Printed by Morris Press Cookbooks, Kearney, NE. 128 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in a black binder with metal rings, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 4. United Methodist Church (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Our Favorite Recipes. Affiliated with the United Methodist Church. Description: Linton, Indiana. ~75 p.: 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 5. United Methodist Women (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Bicentennial Cookbook by United Methodist Women, First United Methodist Church: Bloomington, Indiana. Description: Bloomington, Indiana. Chicago: Women's Clubs Publishing Co., Inc. 61 p.: ill.; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 5)
  - 6. USNAD Crane, Ladies Club (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book: Produce and Pass the Ammunition to our Fighting Fleets. Description: Crane, Indiana. Front cover disconnected. 124 p.: 23 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 5)
  - 7. Vi Krentz (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: When in Rome, Eat Spaghetti with Chopsticks, by Vi Krentz. Title: When in Rome, Eat Spaghetti with Chopsticks, by Vi Krentz. Description: La Porte, Indiana, 1985. 72 p.: ill., index (contents); 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 8. Virginia Hanch (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Ben Davis Centennial: A Taste of Yesteryear. Description: Ben Davis, IN, 1979. By Virginia Hanch. 159 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 9. Zeta Phi Chapter, Kappa Kappa Kappa (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Brown County Cookin'. Title: Brown County Cookin'. Description: Nashville, Indiana, 1978. "Published by Zeta Phi Chapter, Kappa Kappa Kappa, Nashville, Indiana"--Title page. 192 p.: ill.; 22 cm. Black comb bind, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
- IOWA
  - 10. The Assistance League (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Cornerstones a Second Helping: A Cookbook Published by the Assistance League of Marshalltown. Title: Cornerstones a Second Helping: A Cookbook Published by the Asistance League of Marshalltown. Description: Marshalltown, Iowa, 1982. 392 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 11. Harrodsburg Christian Church (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Kentucky's Olde Towne Favorites, 1774-1980. Title: Kentucky's Olde Towne Favorites, The Harrodsburg Christian Church. Description: Harrodsburg, Kentucky, 1980. 212 p.: ill.; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 12. Historical General Dodge House (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Historic General Dodge House Receipts. Title: Historic General Dodge House Receipts. Description: Council Bluffs, Iowa 1976. "Published Spring 1976 by the General's Ladies Board of Directors"-Title page. Includes photographs from the Historic General Dodge House and excerpts from various texts, including The Everyday Cook-Book-1890. 184 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Silver spiral binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 13. Homestead Welfare Club (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Amana Colony Recipes. Spine Title: Amana Colony Recipes. Title: A Collection of Traditional Amana Colony Recipes. Description: Homestead, Iowa, 1976. Compiled by the Ladies Auxiliary of the Homestead Welfare Club. "Family-size recipes of the food prepared and served in the Amana Villages for over a century"-from title page. 120 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 5)
  - 14. The Junior League of Waterloo-Cedar Falls, Iowa (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Pig Out: Selected Recipes from The Junior League of Waterloo-Cedar Falls, Iowa. Spine Title: Pig Out: Selected Recipes from The Junior League of Waterloo-Cedar Falls, Iowa. Title: Pig Out: Selected Recipes from The Junior League of Waterloo-Cedar Falls, Iowa. Description: Pig themed. Waterloo-Cedar Falls, Iowa. Waterloo: WCF Publications, 1986. 256 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Blue wire spiral binding, enclosed in an illustrated board binder. (Box Box 5)
  - 15. The West Branch Heritage Foundation (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Our Rural Heritage: A Collection of Essays and Recipes. Title: Our Rural Heritage: A Collection of Essays and Recipes. Description: West Branch, Iowa, 1976. Published by the West Branch Heritage Foundation. 52 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 5)
- KENTUCKY
  - 16. Anna Elliott Bohon Department of Kentucky Federation of Women's Clubs of Harrodsburg (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Cooking Again...Anna Elliott Bohon Department of the Kentucky Federation of Woman's Clubs of Harrodsburg. Description: 116 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 5)
  - 17. The Courier-Journal and Times Cookbook (Box Box 5)
    - By Lillian Marshall. First Ed., first printing. Louisville, KY: The Courier-Journal and Louisville Times Company, 1971. [3], 4-149 p.: ill., index; 28 cm. Wire spiral bound, with illustrated boards. (Box Box 5)
  - 18. The Courier-Journal Kentucky Cookbook (Box Box 5)
    - Edited by John Finley. Louisville, KY: The Courier-Journal and Louisville Times Company, 1985. [1], 2-327 p.: ill, index; 26 cm. Bound in illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 5)
  - 19. Garden Club of Lexington, Inc. (Box Box 5)
    - Cover Title: Bluegrass Winners: A Cookbook. Spine Title: Bluegrass Winners. Title: Bluegrass Winners: A Cookbook. Description: Lexington, Kentucky, 1985. 350 p.: ill., index; 24 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 5)
  - 1. Irene Hayes (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: What's Cooking in Kentucky. Spine Title: What's Cooking in Kentucky, by Irene Hayes. Title: What's Cooking in Kentucky. Description: 1970. 292 p.: 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover, tabbed sections, and cardboard jacket. (Box Box 6)
  - 2. James B. Haggin Memorial Hospital (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Our Favorite Recipes, James B. Haggin Memorial Hospital. Spine Title: Harrodsburg, Kentucky: Gateway to the West. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes, Compiled by Employees of James B. Haggin Memorial Hospital. Description: Harrodsburg, Kentucky, 1988. 182 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 6)
  - 3. Junior League of Owensboro, Kentucky, Inc. (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: To Market to Market: Junior League of Owensboro, Kentucky, Inc. Spine Title: To Market to Market: Junior League of Owensboro, Kentucky. Description: Pig themed. Owensboro, Kentucky, 1984. 344 p.: cardboard bookmarks, ill., index; 24 cm. Pink comb binding, with illustrated boards. (Box Box 6)
  - 4. Kentucky State Fair (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: The Official 1986/87 Kentucky State Fair Cook Book: Reward Winning Recipes. Spine Title: The Official 1986/87 Kentucky State Fair Cook Book. Title: The Official 1986/87 Kentucky State Fair Cook Book, edited by Deni Hamilton. Description: Award winning recipes from the Kentucky State Fair, 1988. 214 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 6)
  - 5. Kentucky State Parks (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Kentucky: Classic Country Recipes By Pearlie B. Scott. Description: 61 p.: ill.; 22 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 6. Mercer County Humane Society (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Historic Kentucky Recipes: 200 Years of Kentucky Country Cooking. Title: Historic Kentucky Recipes: 200 Years of Kentucky Country Cooking. Compiled by Ms. Ruth Payne through the Mercer County Humane Society. Description: Harrodsburg, Kentucky. 166 p.: ill., index; 28 cm. Red comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 6)
  - 7. The Queen's Daughters, Inc. (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Entertaining the Louisville Way. Title: Entertaining the Louisville Way. Description: Louisville, Kentucky, 1969. Compiled by the Queen's Daughters, Inc. 153 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 6)
  - 8. Renfro Valley (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Favorite Recipes of Renfro Valley by Virginia Sutton. Description: Renfro Valley, Kentucky. 68 p.: 23 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 9. Trustees' House of Pleasant Hill (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Welcome Back to Pleasant Hill: More Recipes from the Trustees' House, Pleasant Hill, Kentucky. Spine Title: Welcome Back to Pleasant Hill~~~Kremer. Title: Welcome Back to Pleasant Hill by Elizabeth C. Kremer. Description:Shaker recipes. Pleasant Hill Press, Harrodsburg, Kentucky, 1977. "Printed in the United States of America by the Keystone Printery, Inc., Lexington, Kentucky"-ii. 89 p.: ill. by Evalina K Settle, index; 22 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 10. Whitley County Extension Homemakers Association (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Homemaker's Delight: Whitley County Extension Homemakers Association. Title: A Book of Favorite Recipes compiled by Whitley County Extension Homemakers Association. Description: Whitley County Extension, Kentucky, 1982. Kansas City: Circulation Service. 118 p.: ill., loose recipes (handwritten and typed), index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 6)
- LOUISIANA
  - 11. The Junior League of Baton Rouge, Inc. (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: River Road Recipes. Spine Title: River Road Recipes. Title: River Road Recipes published by The Junior League of Baton Rouge, Inc. Description: Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1959. Baton Rouge: The Junior League of Baton Rouge, Inc., 1977. 262 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 6)
  - 12. Trinity Lutheran Church (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Trinity Lutheran Church, St. Joseph, Michigan Cook Book by Ladies Aid Society. Description: 148 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 6)
- MICHIGAN
  - 13. Meadow Brook Hall (Box Box 6)
    - Spine Title: Meadow Brook Hall Cookbook. Title: Meadow Brook Hall Cookbook. Description: Meadow Brook Hall: Oakland University; Rochester, Michigan. 217 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Brown comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 6)
- MINNESOTA
  - 14. Circle "D" of Bethel Lutheran Church Ladies Aid (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book, 1933. Description: Willmar, Minnesota, 1933. 70 p.: ill.,; 23 cm. In wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 15. First Congregational Church (Box Box 6)
    - Title: Cook Book. Description: Mankato, Minnesota, 1951. Compiled by the Pilgrimettes of First Congregational Church. 115 p.: ill., index; 18 cm. In wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 16. First Lutheran Ladies' Aid Society, Third Division (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Over 500 Home Tested Recipes. Title: Over Five Hundred Home Tested Recipes. Description: Ada, Minnesota, 1927. Compiled by the Third Division First Lutheran Ladies' Aid Society. Inscribed, "Rachel Ahlers." 140 p.: ill.,; 22 cm. Bound in wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 17. Ladies Aid Society of the Congregational Church (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Cook Book of Favorite and Tested Recipes. Title: Cook Book of Favorite and Tested Recipes. Description: Ada, Minnesota, 1931 (?). Inscribed, "Mrs. E. J. Wigley-1931." Published by Second Division, Congregational Ladies Aid Society. 98 p.: ill. (inside ads); 12 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 18. Mankato State University Faculty Wives (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Festivity Feasting from Faculty Wives, Mankato State University, Mankato, Minnesota. Title: Festivity Feasting from Faculty Wives, Mankato State University, Mankato, Minnesota. Description: Mankato, Minnesota, 1985. Inscribed to June, October, 1985. 318 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 6)
  - 19. Minnesota Valley Restoration Project (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: The Homesteader's Cook Book. Title: The Homesteader's Cook Book. Description: Shakopee, Minnesota, 1971. "A collection of recipes and memorabilia from the Minnesota River Valley area"-from page [3]. Edited and compiled by Ginger Timmons, with illustrates by John Mcguire and photographs by Leroy Lebens. 156 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 6)
  - 20. Vinje Lutheran Church (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: The Mixing Bowl. Description: Willmar, Minnesota, 1949 (?). Inscribed, "Best wishes, from, Mary Gergerson, 1949" and "Mrs Roy Hendreckson." 144 p.: ill.,; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 6)
- MISSOURI
  - 21. The Advertiser-Courier (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Aus der Hermannhuche: From Hermann's Kitchens. Description: Hermann, MO, 1987. Published by the Advertiser-Courier. 79 p.: ill.; 28 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 22. Branson (Box Box 6)
    - Cover Title: Branson Cookin' Country: Featuring Restaurants and Recipes from America's Country Music Capital - By Susan St. Marie-Martin. Spine Title: Branson Cookin' Country: Featuring Restaurants and Recipes from America's Country Music Capital - By Susan St. Marie-Martin. Title 1: Branson Cookin' Country. Title 2: Branson Cookin' Country: Featuring Restaurants and Recipes from America's Country Music Capital - By Susan St. Marie-Martin. Description: Kansas City: Two Lane Press, 1993. 97 p.: map, restaurant locations, restaurant index, recipe index; 23 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 6)
  - 1. The Shaw House (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: The Shaw House Cook Book: A Collection of Choice Receipts from a Golden Era of St. Louis Living. Title: The Shaw House Cook Book: Being a collection of choice receipts gathered during the past century in St. Louis and revised for modern living. Description: St. Louis, Missouri, 1963. Edited by Marian Maeve O'Brien. Published by the Historical Committee and the Women's Association of Missouri Botanical Garden, St. Luis, Missouri. 254 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated covers. (Box Box 7)
- NEW MEXICO
  - 2. Albuquerque Dental Auxiliary (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Seasoned with Sunshine. Title: Seasoned with Sunshine: Recipes collected and tested by the Albuquerque Dental Auxiliary. Description: Albuquerque, New Mexico, 1964. 138 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. Green comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 7)
  - 3. Roswell Symphony Guild (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Savoring the Southwest. Spine Title: Savoring the Southwest. Title: Savoring the Southwest. Symphony Guild Cookbook. Description: Roswell, New Mexico, 1983. Rosewell: Roswell Symphony Guild Publications. 329 p.: ill., index; 27 cm. Bound in illustrated boards. (Box Box 7)
- NEW YORK
  - 4. Southampton Garden Club (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Southampton Garden Club Cookbook. Title: Southampton Garden Club Cookbook. Description: Southampton, NY, 1979. Illustrations by Mrs. H Rogers Benjamin. 140 p.: ill.; 23 cm. (Box Box 7)
- NORTH CAROLINA
  - 5. The Junior League of Fayetteville, Inc. (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: The Carolina Collection, The Junior League of Fayetteville, Inc. Spine Title: The Carolina Collection. Title: The Carolina Collection, The Junior League of Fayetteville, Inc. Description: Fayetteville, North Carolina, 1978. Cover Design and Illustrations by E. Janet Parks. "Printed in the United States of America-- Memphis: Wimmer Brothers Fine Printing and Lithography-from title verso. 320 p.: ill., index; 23 cm. White comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 7)
- NORTH DAKOTA
  - 6. Hamilton German Café (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: I Ate at the German Café, Hamilton, N.D.: Our Favorite Recipes. Description: Hamilton, North Dakota. Collierville: Fundcraft Publishing, Inc. 144 p.: ill., index; 22 cm. Black comb binding, with illustrated front cover. (Box Box 7)
  - 7. North Dakota State Wheat Commission (Box Box 7)
    - Cover Title: Dakota Delectables. Description: Bismarck, ND. 24 p.; 20 cm. In illustrated wrappers. (Box Box 7)
- PENNSYLVANIA
  - 8. A. Monroe Aurand, Jr. (Box Box 7)